How do you hold on to someone you've never met?
The Lake House is a drama, mystery, romance film directed by Alejandro Agresti.
A lonely doctor who once occupied an unusual lakeside home begins exchanging
love letters with its former resident, a frustrated architect.
They must try to unravel the mystery behind their
extraordinary romance before it's too late.
Alex Wyler, played by Keanu Reeves.
Kate Forster, played by Sandra Bullock.
Simon Wyler, played by Christopher Plummer.
Henry Wyler, played by Ebon Moss-Bachrach.
Kate's Mother, played by Willeke van Ammelrooy.
Morgan, played by Dylan Walsh.
The Lake House is a 2006 American fantasy romance film directed
by Alejandro Agresti and written by David Auburn.
A remake of the 2000 South Korean film Il Mare, it stars Keanu Reeves and Sandra
Bullock, who last appeared together in the 1994 action thriller film Speed.
The film revolves around an architect (Reeves) living in 2004 and a doctor (Bullock) living in 2006 who meet via
letters left in the mailbox of a lake house where they both lived at separate points in time.
They carry on a two-year correspondence while
remaining separated by the time difference.
The film explores themes of chicago, illinois,
future, ex-boyfriend, writing, architect.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.